Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not Annotated
      - R
        - Rev Run - I used to think I was run, 2005; SR-29501; Rev Run (Box 412)
          Catalog # DEFR 16444-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16444-1-A-1
          Russell Simmons Music Group
        - Rev Run - Mind on the road, 2005; SR-29502; Rev Run (Box 412)
          Catalog # DEFR 16336-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR 16336-1 -2
        - Rev Run - I used to think I was run, 2005; SR-29503; Rev Run (Box 412)
        - Revival - I know he will, 1995; SR-29504; Revival (Box 412)
          Catalog # SR12387; A-side Matrix # SR12387
        - Revoked - Pieces, 1989; SR-29505; Revoked (Box 412)
          Catalog # HMF-117; A-side Matrix # HMF-117-A
          Hot Mix 5 Records
        - Revolutionary Suicide - Revelation; Rotation, 1995; SR-29506; Revolutionary Suicide (Box 412)
          Catalog # RS-0403; A-side Matrix # RS-0403-B VP-CM
          Exile Records
        - Rex Riddem - Salavador diaspora, 2005; SR-29507; Rex Riddem (Box 412)
          In same jacket as # SR-29508; SR-29509. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FKX-006; A-side Matrix # 0506X49 A A+R SDGII FKX 006 A
          TrueGrooves Productions
        - Rex Riddem - Salavador diaspora, 2005; SR-29508; Rex Riddem (Box 412)
          In same jacket as # SR-29507; SR-29509. 2 copies.
          Fort Knox Recordings
        - Kidgusto - Heat beats, 2005; SR-29509; Kidgusto (Box 412)
          In same jacket as # SR-29507; SR-29508. Different discs.
          Catalog # TG-002; A-side Matrix # TG-002 A
        - Reynolds, Barry - I scare myself, 1982; SR-29510; Reynolds, Barry (Box 412)
          Catalog # 90011-1; A-side Matrix # SP STIL 824983-A 0-1 SM1-1
        - Reynolds, L.J. - Special effects, 1982; SR-29511; Reynolds, L.J. (Box 412)
          Catalog # SPRO-9807; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9807-98262 G-1
        - Reynolds, L.J. - Special effects, 1982; SR-29512; Reynolds, L.J. (Box 413)
        - Reynolds, Margaret - Take me to the moon, 1980; SR-29513; Reynolds, Margaret; KC (Box 413)
          Catalog # SSD-4217; A-side Matrix # SSD-4217A3
          Sunshine Sound Disco
        - Reynos - Tato OK, 2004; SR-29514; Reynos (Box 413)
          Catalog # UBO-1028-0; A-side Matrix # UBO-1028-2-A
          Urban Box Office
        - Reynos - Tato OK, 2004; SR-29515; Reynos (Box 413)
          Catalog # S 54024; A-side Matrix # 8869-1002-1(1) S-54024
          Latinflava
        - Rezidue - Inner city blues, 1997; SR-29516; Rezidue (Box 413)
          Catalog # DB-5002; A-side Matrix # DB-5002 A F/W RCE
          DataBase Recordings
        - ラッパ我リヤ - R.G. Riki-Gaku, 1999; SR-29517; ラッパ我リヤ; Rappagariya (Box 413)
          Catalog # SOML-0005; A-side Matrix # SOML0005A
          走馬党 Entertainment
        - ラッパ我リヤ - R.G. Riki-Gaku, 1999; SR-29518; ラッパ我リヤ; Rappagariya (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29519. 2 copies.
        - ラッパ我リヤ - R.G. Riki-Gaku, 1999; SR-29519; ラッパ我リヤ; Rappagariya (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29518. 2 copies.
        - Rhamel - Power; Peace (remix), 1990; SR-29520; Rhamel (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29521. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 49 73167; A-side Matrix # XSS 73167 A-1A
          Rhyme $yndicate Records
        - Rhamel - Power; Peace (remix), 1990; SR-29521; Rhamel (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29520. 2 copies.
        - Rheingold - Via satellit, 1983; SR-29522; Rheingold (Box 413)
          Catalog # A 12.3882; A-side Matrix # NL CBSA 12.3882 A2
          CBS
        - Rhythm - I'll do anything for you, 1991; SR-29524; Rhythm (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29525. Different discs.Promo
          Catalog # NAS 4154; A-side Matrix # XSS-4154-A 1A DMS
          WTG Records
        - Rhythm - I'll do anything for you; Feel the groove, 1991; SR-29525; Rhythm (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29524. Different discs.
          Catalog # 41 73822; A-side Matrix # XSS-73822A-1A G1 (T)
        - Rhythm, Jonny - Let it go (we like so), 1986; SR-29526; Rhythm, Jonny (Box 413)
          Catalog # CBED 005; A-side Matrix # CBED-005 A1 B+B Music
          Caribbean Echo
        - Rhythm Masters - The underground (Disc one), 2001; SR-29527; Rhythm Masters (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29528. Double album.
          Catalog # tb2247; A-side Matrix # TB-2247-A
          Tommy Boy Silver Label
        - Rhythm Masters - The underground (Disc two), 2001; SR-29528; Rhythm Masters (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29527. Double album.
          Catalog # tb2247; A-side Matrix # TB-2247-C
        - Rhythm Section - Feelin' happy, 1995; SR-29529; Rhythm Section; Harding, Bobby (Box 413)
          Catalog # CH 11003-DJ; A-side Matrix # CH 11003 A
          Choice Records
        - Rhythm to Rhythm - Sounds of rhythm EP volume #1 - sureshot mixes, 1994; SR-29530; Rhythm to Rhythm (Box 413)
          Catalog # MP003; A-side Matrix # MP-003-RHYTHMSIDE
          Muzik Pushers
        - Rhythmcentric - You don't have to worry, 1996; SR-29531; Rhythmcentric (Box 413)
          Catalog # MRCTAZ 8011; A-side Matrix # MRC TAZ -8011-A
          Tazmania Records
        - Tha Rhythum - Mic check; Throw dem boes, 1999; SR-29532; Tha Rhythum (Box 413)
          Catalog # 0267-1; A-side Matrix # 0267-1
          Benz Records Inc.
          Stone Mountain, Georgia
        - Ric-A-Che - Coo-coo che; Lil bro, 2003; SR-29533; Ric-A-Che (Box 413)
          Catalog # UNIR 21102-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR 211021-A
        - Ric-A-Che - Coo-coo che; Lil bro, 2003; SR-29534; Ric-A-Che (Box 413)
        - Ric-A-Che - Lack of communication (Disc one), 2004; SR-29535; Ric-A-Che (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29536. Double album.
          Catalog # B0002740-01; A-side Matrix # B0002740-01 LP1 A RE-1
        - Ric-A-Che - Lack of communication (Disc two), 2004; SR-29536; Ric-A-Che (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29535. Double album.
          Catalog # B0002740-01; A-side Matrix # B0002740-01 LP2 A RE-1 (SIDE C)
        - Rice And Beans - What's the beef, 1980; SR-29538; Rice And Beans (Box 413)
          Catalog # MS-1717; A-side Matrix # MS1717A
          Casanova Records
        - Rich Boy - D-Boyz, 2005; SR-29539; Rich Boy (Box 413)
          Catalog # INTR-11355-1; A-side Matrix # INTR 11355-1-REI A
        - Richard, Cliff - Wired for sound, 1981; SR-29540; Richard, Cliff (Box 413)
          Catalog # SW-17059; A-side Matrix # SW-1-17059 Z F5
        - Riches, Suzann - Hungry for your love, 1984; SR-29541; Riches, Suzann (Box 413)
          Catalog # SF 204; A-side Matrix # SF-204-A
          Savoir Faire Records
        - Richards, Keith - Take it so hard, 1988; SR-29542; Richards, Keith (Box 413)
          Catalog # PR 2395; A-side Matrix # STPR 56053-1 1-1
        - Richie, Lionel - Dancing on the ceiling, 1986; SR-29543; Richie, Lionel (Box 413)
          Catalog # ZL72412; A-side Matrix # DM B-5514 A-1/7-86 IV
        - Richie, Lionel - Lionel Richie, 1982; SR-29544; Richie, Lionel (Box 413)
          Catalog # 6007ML; A-side Matrix # 6007-ML-A-15C S-13 ZNA BMU
        - Richie, Lionel - Can't slow down, 1983; SR-29545; Richie, Lionel (Box 413)
          Catalog # 6059ML; A-side Matrix # 6059ML-A- 15AZJC#13 EPZE
        - Richie Rich - Do g's get to go to heaven?, 1996; SR-29546; Richie Rich (Box 413)
          Catalog # 314 574 031-1; A-side Matrix # 314 574 031-1 A
        - Richie Rich - If…; Straight mail, 1998; SR-29547; Richie Rich (Box 413)
          Catalog # DEF 302-1; A-side Matrix # DEF-302-1-A-REI
        - Richie Rich - Rockin' on the go go scene, 1989; SR-29548; Richie Rich (Box 413)
          Catalog # GEET 12; A-side Matrix # GEET-12-A-1
          Gee Street
        - Richie Rich - My DJ (pump it up some) (club mix), 1988; SR-29549; Richie Rich (Box 413)
          Catalog # GEE T7; A-side Matrix # GEE T-7-A1 MIKE'S
        - Richie Rich - My DJ (pump it up some) (club mix), 1988; SR-29550; Richie Rich (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29551. Different discs.
        - Richie Rich - My DJ (pump it up some) (remix), 1988; SR-29551; Richie Rich (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29550. Different discs.
          Catalog # GEE T7R; A-side Matrix # ADRENALIN- GEE7-TR-A1 PAG
        - Richie Rich - I can make you dance, 1989; SR-29552; Richie Rich (Box 413)
          Catalog # GEE T22; A-side Matrix # GEE-T-22 A2 ADRENALIN
        - Richie Rich - Do g's get to go to heaven?, 1996; SR-29553; Richie Rich (Box 413)
          Catalog # Do G's #1; A-side Matrix # Do G's #1A
        - Rick - When you gonna, 1987; SR-29554; Rick; Lisa (Box 413)
          Catalog # 6548-1-RDAB; A-side Matrix # 6548 1 RD A 1 2
        - Riff - White men can't jump, 1992; SR-29555; Riff (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29556. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SPRO-05448; A-side Matrix # SPRO-05448-A 1-1
          SBK Records
        - Riff - White men can't jump, 1992; SR-29556; Riff (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29555. 2 copies.
        - Right N' Exact - Da mornin afta; Dragonz; Skratch this; Imposters; Truth is truth, 1999; SR-29557; Right N' Exact; Hated Family (Box 413)
          Catalog # CCX0002; A-side Matrix # CCX-0002-A
          210 Records
          San Antonio, Texas
        - Rihanna - Music of the sun (Disc one), 2005; SR-29558; Rihanna (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29559. Double album.
          Catalog # B0004937-01; A-side Matrix # B0004937-01-LP1A RJ
        - Rihanna - Music of the sun (Disc two), 2005; SR-29559; Rihanna (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29558. Double album.
          Catalog # B0004937-01; A-side Matrix # B0004937-01-LP2A RJ
        - Rihanna - Pon de replay, 2005; SR-29560; Rihanna (Box 413)
          Catalog # DEFR 16306-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR 16306-1A RJ
        - Rihanna - If it's lovin' that you want, 2005; SR-29561; Rihanna (Box 413)
          Catalog # DEFR 16362-1; A-side Matrix # B0005342-11-A RJ
        - Rihanna - S.O.S., 2005; SR-29562; Rihanna (Box 413)
          Catalog # DEFR 16474-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16474-1A RJ
        - Rihanna - If it's lovin' that you want (remix), 2005; SR-29563; Rihanna; Corey Gunz (Box 413)
          Catalog # DEFR 16446-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16446-1A RJ
        - Rihanna - Pon de replay (remix), 2005; SR-29564; Rihanna (Box 413)
          Catalog # DEFR 16358-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16358-1A RJ
        - Rihanna - If it's lovin' that you want, 2005; SR-29565; Rihanna (Box 413)
        - Rihanna - Pon de replay (remix), 2005; SR-29566; Rihanna (Box 413)
        - Rikii The Lunatic Lady - Funkii AfroDeezo; The lunatic lady; First blood, 1998; SR-29567; Rikii The Lunatic Lady (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29568. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ECHO2295; A-side Matrix # ECHO2295-A
          Meridian Music
        - Rikii The Lunatic Lady - Funkii AfroDeezo; The lunatic lady; First blood, 1998; SR-29568; Rikii The Lunatic Lady (Box 413)
          In same jacket as # SR-29567. 2 copies.
        - Rikki - Breakaway, 1988; SR-29569; Rikki (Box 414)
          Catalog # LMR 6000; A-side Matrix # LMR-6000-RE A F/W
          LMR (Lefrak-Moelis Records)
        - Riley, Jimmy - Reggae super star, 1978; SR-29570; Riley, Jimmy (Box 414)
          Catalog # LP-9043; A-side Matrix # A C-9043
          Camille Records
        - Riley, Melvin - Whose is it?, 1994; SR-29571; Riley, Melvin (Box 414)
          Catalog # MCA8P 3019; A-side Matrix # MCA 11959 FDS-2
        - Riley, Teddy - My fantasy (extended version) (music from "Do The Right Thing"), 1989; SR-29572; Riley, Teddy; Guy (Box 414)
          Catalog # MOT-4643; A-side Matrix # MOT-4643-HF1
        - Rinder & Lewis - Envy (animal fire), 1978; SR-29573; Rinder & Lewis (Box 414)
          Catalog # PRO-12-206-D; A-side Matrix # 058-12-206-A K-9809 GOL
          AVI Records
        - Ring - Call me; Theme from "The Saint", 1981; SR-29574; Ring (Box 414)
          Catalog # SPV 40; A-side Matrix # SPV 40A-1A
          Vanguard Disco
        - Ringo, Johnny - Sip a sip; Buenos dias, 1982; SR-29575; Ringo, Johnny (Box 414)
          Catalog # ARC0003; A-side Matrix # ARC0003-A-DT
          Absissa
        - Ringo, Johnnie - Riding west, 1982; SR-29576; Ringo, Johnnie (Box 414)
          Catalog # VPRLP 1012; A-side Matrix # VPRLP 1012-A
        - Ringo, Johnnie - Hot number, 1982; SR-29577; Ringo, Johnnie (Box 414)
          Catalog # none; A-side Matrix # AI-012-A HoT NUMBER
          Mr. O Production
        - Ringo, Johnny - The boss; Moses, 1981; SR-29584; Ringo, Johnny (Box 414)
          Catalog # none; A-side Matrix # C P 8 3 82 THE BOSS RINGO
          Black & White
        - Riperton, Minnie - The best of Minnie Riperton, 1981; SR-29578; Riperton, Minnie (Box 414)
          Catalog # ST-12189; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12189 F 4 X538
        - Ripper - Still in the mood, 1994; SR-29579; Ripper (Box 414)
          Catalog # FT-7; A-side Matrix # FT-7-A
          Flame Tameless Records
          Hollis, New York
        - Ripper - Still in the mood, 1994; SR-29580; Ripper (Box 414)
        - Ripple - The beat goes on and on, 1977; SR-29581; Ripple (Box 414)
          Catalog # SG 2057; A-side Matrix # SG 2057 A JR
          Salsoul Records
        - Risqué - Starlight; The girls are back in town, 1982; SR-29582; Risqué (Box 414)
          Catalog # MP-317; A-side Matrix # MP-317-A
          Importe/12
        - Risqué - Burn it up, Mr. DJ, 1983; SR-29583; Risqué (Box 414)
          Catalog # MP-323; A-side Matrix # MP-323-A
        - Risco Connections - Its my house; Risco version, 1979; SR-29585; Risco Connections; Isaacs, Joe (Box 414)
          Catalog # ARK DD 023; A-side Matrix # ARKDD-023 A
          Arawak
        - Risto Benji - Passport buddy, 1991; SR-29586; Risto Benji (Box 414)
          Catalog # FS-05; A-side Matrix # FS 005-A
          Father & Son Records
        - Rita Mitsouko - Marcia baïla, 1984; SR-29587; Rita Mitsouko (Box 414)
          Catalog # 80149; A-side Matrix # MPO I 80149 A 10
        - Rita Mitsouko - Hip kit, 1990; SR-29588; Rita Mitsouko (Box 414)
          Catalog # VST 1296; A-side Matrix # D VST 1296 B-1U-1-1 Town House DMM
        - Rita Mitsouko - Andy, 1987; SR-29589; Rita Mitsouko (Box 414)
          Catalog # DMD 1134; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-53512-1
        - Ritchie Family - All night all right, 1983; SR-29590; Ritchie Family (Box 414)
          Catalog # AFL1-4601; A-side Matrix # AFL-1 -4601- A -3
        - Ritchie Family - Bad reputation, 1979; SR-29591; Ritchie Family (Box 414)
          Catalog # NBLP 7166-DJ; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7166-AS-REI-PRC-C3
        - Ritchie Family - Brazil, 1975; SR-29592; Ritchie Family (Box 414)
          In same jacket as # SR-29593. 2 copies.
          Catalog # T-498; A-side Matrix # 20TH CENTURY FOX-M-498-AS
          20th Century Records
        - Ritchie Family - Brazil, 1975; SR-29593; Ritchie Family (Box 414)
          In same jacket as # SR-29592. 2 copies.
        - Ritchie Family - I'll do my best (for you baby), 1982; SR-29594; Ritchie Family (Box 414)
          Catalog # JT-13093; A-side Matrix # PD-13093-A-1
        - Ritchie Family - Countdown (Captain Fingers), 1981; SR-29595; Ritchie Family (Box 414)
          Catalog # AS-11515; A-side Matrix # AS-11515-A-SP 1-1
        - Ritchie Family - Rit, 1981; SR-29596; Ritchie Family (Box 414)
          Catalog # 6E-331; A-side Matrix # 6E-331-A4-SH-SP 579 B-15483 SP 0-1
        - Ritz - Locomotion, 1979; SR-29597; Ritz (Box 414)
          Catalog # 48-50731; A-side Matrix # 48-50731
        - Ritz - I wanna get with you, 1980; SR-29598; Ritz (Box 414)
          Catalog # POS 1201; A-side Matrix # POS-1201-A
          Posse Records
        - Ritz - Workin' out, 1981; SR-29599; Ritz (Box 414)
          In same jacket as # SR-29600. 2 copies.
          Catalog # POS 1203; A-side Matrix # POS-1203-A-1658
        - Ritz - Workin' out, 1981; SR-29600; Ritz (Box 414)
          In same jacket as # SR-29599. 2 copies.
        - Ritz - Workin' out, 1981; SR-29601; Ritz (Box 414)
        - Rival - Rival CNN, 1999; SR-29602; Rival (Box 414)
          Catalog # EPC 668336 6; A-side Matrix # 668 3366000A1
          Belgium
        - Rival - Rival CNN, 1999; SR-29603; Rival (Box 414)
        - Rival - D'un monde a l'autre, 1999; SR-29604; Rival (Box 414)
          Catalog # EPC 667200 6; A-side Matrix # oo72006000 1A1
        - Rival - L'Overture, 1997; SR-29605; Rival (Box 414)
          Catalog # CNN001; A-side Matrix # CNN 001 A1 DP
          Souterrain
        - ROTM - Lost in the mind, 1995; SR-29606; ROTM; Rivals of the Mind (Box 414)
          Catalog # LNR1002; A-side Matrix # LNR-1002 A F/W GSV
          LNR Records
        - ROTM - Lost in the mind, 1995; SR-29607; ROTM; Rivals of the Mind (Box 414)
        - ROTM - Lost in the mind, 1995; SR-29608; ROTM; Rivals of the Mind (Box 414)
        - Rivas - Oye, 1982; SR-29609; Rivas (Box 414)
          Catalog # K-722; A-side Matrix # K-722-A
          Kim Records
          West New York, New Jersey
        - Rivera, Hector - Hecto-mania, 1970; SR-29610; Rivera, Hector (Box 414)
          Catalog # FP 1236; A-side Matrix # FP 1236 A R-1 2 20 70 MS
          4 Points
        - Rivera, Robby - El sorullo - the remixes, 1996; SR-29611; Rivera, Robby (Box 414)
          Catalog # JR0296; A-side Matrix # JR-0296-A
          Juicy Records
        - Rix, Jerry - Disco train, 1977; SR-29612; Rix, Jerry (Box 414)
          Catalog # AVID-12-132; A-side Matrix # 12-132-A K-7896 GOL
        - R.J.'s Latest Arrival - Wind me up, 1980; SR-29613; R.J.'s Latest Arrival (Box 414)
          Catalog # DSC 144; A-side Matrix # DSC-144-SA-CT1
          Buddah Records
        - R.J.'s Latest Arrival - Hold on, 1986; SR-29614; R.J.'s Latest Arrival (Box 414)
          Catalog # V-56042; A-side Matrix # V-1-56042-241042-Z1
          Manhattan Records
        - R.J.'s Latest Arrival - Could have been you, 1988; SR-29615; R.J.'s Latest Arrival (Box 414)
          Catalog # V-56112; A-side Matrix # V-1-56112-Z1
        - R.J.'s Latest Arrival - Rhythm method (R.J.'s revenge), 1986; SR-29616; R.J.'s Latest Arrival (Box 414)
          Catalog # V-56048; A-side Matrix # V-1-56048-241041 E-Z2
        - R.J.'s Latest Arrival - Does she do it like she dances, 1979; SR-29617; R.J.'s Latest Arrival (Box 414)
          Catalog # PRO 7758; A-side Matrix # PRO-7758-AS
          Ariola Records America
        - R.J.'s Latest Arrival - Swing low, 1985; SR-29618; R.J.'s Latest Arrival (Box 414)
          Catalog # DMD 847; A-side Matrix # ST DM 47834-47836-3 1-2
        - R.J.'s Latest Arrival - Body snatcher, 1981; SR-29619; R.J.'s Latest Arrival (Box 414)
          Catalog # SUD 004; A-side Matrix # SUD-004-A
          Sutra Records
        - R.J.'s Latest Arrival - Harmony, 1984; SR-29620; R.J.'s Latest Arrival (Box 414)
          Catalog # GBLP 1; A-side Matrix # GOLDEN BOY SIDE-A GBLP 1
          Golden Boy Records
        - R.L. Project - My house is lifted, 1997; SR-29621; R.L. Project (Box 414)
          Test pressing
          Catalog # CR-410-DJ; A-side Matrix # CR-410-A
          Cutting Records
        - RMB - Shadows, 1998; SR-29622; RMB; Sharam (Box 415)
          Catalog # 7432155226 1; A-side Matrix # RMB-FEAT SHADOW-11 SHADOWS -A
          Low Spirit Recordings
          Berlin, Germany
        - RMB - Shadows, 1998; SR-29623; RMB; Sharam (Box 415)
          Catalog # 74321 55226 1; A-side Matrix # B81033-01 A1 MK
        - RMB - Break the silence; Everything, 1997; SR-29624; RMB (Box 415)
          Catalog # 74321 49234 1; A-side Matrix # 743 214 923 41-A1
        - RMB - Shadows, 1998; SR-29625; RMB; Sharam (Box 415)
        - RN Plus 1 - Like a vampire, 1999; SR-29626; RN Plus 1 (Box 415)
          Catalog # 74321 69146 1; A-side Matrix # B924752-01 A1 KL
          Nextfire Recordings
        - RN Plus 1 - Like a vampire, 1999; SR-29627; RN Plus 1 (Box 415)
        - RN Plus 1 - Like a vampire, 1999; SR-29628; RN Plus 1 (Box 415)
        - Rob-n-Steal - When I say; Life on the line (remix), 1997; SR-29671; Rob-n-Steal (Box 415)
          Catalog # PRO-7450-0; A-side Matrix # PRO-7450-0A PH-2-97
        - Robie Man - Monster, 1997; SR-29629; Robie Man (Box 415)
          In same jacket as # SR-29630. 2 copies.
          Catalog # none; A-side Matrix # MONSTER SIDE A
          Wrekanize Records
          Shaker Heights, Ohio
        - Robie Man - Monster, 1997; SR-29630; Robie Man (Box 415)
          In same jacket as # SR-29629. 2 copies.
        - Roachford - Roachford, 1988; SR-29631; Roachford (Box 415)
          Catalog # E 45097; A-side Matrix # AL-45097-C-1 DMM DMS
        - Robaleé - Uh-uh, u satisfy, 1991; SR-29632; Robaleé (Box 415)
          Catalog # RA 0200; A-side Matrix # RA-0300-A
          Rave Records
        - Robaleé - Uh-uh, u satisfy, 1991; SR-29633; Robaleé (Box 415)
        - Robert S. - Don't dis me, 1986; SR-29634; Robert S. (Box 415)
          Catalog # 49 05994; A-side Matrix # XSS175635-1A A5
        - Robert S. - Good as gold; Big words, 1987; SR-29635; Robert S. (Box 415)
          In same jacket as # SR-29636. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 49-06860; A-side Matrix # XSS176168-1A G1
        - Robert S. - Good as gold; Big words, 1987; SR-29636; Robert S. (Box 415)
          In same jacket as # SR-29635. 2 copies.
        - Roberts, Laurie - Your key fits, 1984; SR-29637; Roberts, Laurie (Box 415)
          Includes promotional materials
          Catalog # BR 702; A-side Matrix # BR 702 A
          Baywest Records
          Marina del Rey, California
        - Robertson, Dave - Liquidity, 2000; SR-29638; Robertson, Dave (Box 415)
          Catalog # TX419; A-side Matrix # TX 419-A
          Trax Records
        - Robertson, Dave - Liquidity, 2000; SR-29639; Robertson, Dave (Box 415)
        - Robertson, Dave - Liquidity, 2000; SR-29640; Robertson, Dave (Box 415)
        - Robertson, Dave - Liquidity, 2000; SR-29641; Robertson, Dave (Box 415)
        - Robertson, Martin - Rub-a-dub-a-all night, 1988; SR-29642; Robertson, Martin (Box 415)
          Catalog # MR-J-001; A-side Matrix # MRJ-0001A RUB-A-DUB-A ALL NIGHT
          Juledd
        - Robi Rob's Clubworld - Shake that body (Disc one), 1996; SR-29643; Robi Rob's Clubworld (Box 415)
          In same jacket as # SR-29644; SR-29645. Triple album.
          Catalog # 44 78393; A-side Matrix # XSS-78393-A
        - Robi Rob's Clubworld - Shake that body (Disc two), 1996; SR-29644; Robi Rob's Clubworld (Box 415)
          In same jacket as # SR-29643; SR-29645. Triple album.
          Catalog # 44 78393; A-side Matrix # XSS-78394-A
        - Robi Rob's Clubworld - Shake that body (Disc three), 1996; SR-29645; Robi Rob's Clubworld (Box 415)
          In same jacket as # SR-29643; SR-29644. Triple album.
          Catalog # 44 78393; A-side Matrix # XSS-78395-A
        - Robinson, Bert - I promise you love, 1989; SR-29646; Robinson, Bert (Box 415)
          Catalog # C1-90801; A-side Matrix # C1-1-9080-DMM-=1
        - Robinson, Bert - No more cold nights, 1987; SR-29647; Robinson, Bert (Box 415)
          Catalog # CLX-46921; A-side Matrix # CLX-1-46921-Z2 B-28603-Z2 17676 SPO-1 AL-SP
        - Robinson, Jackie - Pussyfooter; I can't stop, 1977; SR-29648; Robinson, Jackie; Davis, John (Box 415)
          Catalog # 100; A-side Matrix # PUSSYFOOTER 100A
          White Rock Records
        - Robinson, Jackie - Pussyfooter; I can't stop, 1977; SR-29649; Robinson, Jackie; Davis, John (Box 415)
        - Robinson, James - Can we do it again, 1987; SR-29650; Robinson, James (Box 415)
          Catalog # ZAS 2749; A-side Matrix # XSS-176158-1A G1
          Tabu Records